{
    "subject": "resource/Chico_Hamilton_Trio",
    "predicate": "ontology/recordLabel",
    "object": "resource/Pacific_Jazz_Records",
    "human_readable": "The Chico Hamilton Trio was recorded by Pacific Jazz Records.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9009667634963989,
            "question": "Is the Chico Hamilton Trio a jazz group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8703646063804626,
            "question": "Name a jazz group recorded by Pacific Jazz Records."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8606889843940735,
            "question": "Who was recorded by Pacific Jazz Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8535596132278442,
            "question": "What was the name of the record label that recorded the Chico Hamilton Trio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8195132613182068,
            "question": "What record label released music by the Chico Hamilton Trio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8127472996711731,
            "question": "Who were some artists recorded by Pacific Jazz Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7944669127464294,
            "question": "Which musical group had their recordings released by Pacific Jazz Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6911076903343201,
            "question": "Pacific Jazz Records is known for recording which genre of music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6633530855178833,
            "question": "With which label is the Chico Hamilton Trio associated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6320105791091919,
            "question": "What type of music did Pacific Jazz Records release?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Chico Hamilton Trio was recorded by Pacific Jazz Records.",
            "html": "dbpedia_876_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=With which label is the Chico Hamilton Trio associated?",
            "html": "dbpedia_876_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pacific Jazz Records is known for recording which genre of music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_876_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which musical group had their recordings released by Pacific Jazz Records?",
            "html": "dbpedia_876_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_876_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_876_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_876_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_876_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_876_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_876_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_876_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_876_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_876_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_876_65.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe document states \"In fact, Mulligan\u2019s quartet was the first group recorded by an indie record label on the West Coast named Pacific Jazz.\" and later mentions \"World Pacific Records WP-1258\" in relation to a Chico Hamilton album.  This strongly implies that both Mulligan's Quartet and The Chico Hamilton Trio were recorded by Pacific Jazz Records. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Chico Hamilton formed the Chico Hamilton Quintet, and there are specific albums listed such as \"Chico Hamilton Quintet\" (1956), which were recorded by Pacific Jazz. This information supports the statement that the Chico Hamilton Trio was recorded by Pacific Jazz Records."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}